{
  "modes": {
    "addition": {
      "best": {
        "score": 1,
        "total": 3,
        "timestamp": "2025-11-03T16:36:05.401910Z",
        "questions": [
          {
            "problem": "50 + 38 = ?",
            "answer": 88,
            "user": 123,
            "correct": false
          },
          {
            "problem": "95 + 93 = ?",
            "answer": 188,
            "user": 123,
            "correct": false
          },
          {
            "problem": "49 + 41 = ?",
            "answer": 90,
            "user": 90,
            "correct": true
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "subtraction": {
      "best": {
        "score": 1,
        "total": 2,
        "timestamp": "2025-11-01T06:55:08.140430Z",
        "questions": [
          {
            "problem": "50 - 29 = ?",
            "answer": 21,
            "user": 21,
            "correct": true
          },
          {
            "problem": "53 - 26 = ?",
            "answer": 27,
            "user": 32,
            "correct": false
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "multiplication": {
      "best": {
        "score": 5,
        "total": 5,
        "timestamp": "2025-11-01T06:48:49.199871Z",
        "questions": [
          {
            "problem": "4 × 5 = ?",
            "answer": 20,
            "user": 20,
            "correct": true
          },
          {
            "problem": "5 × 1 = ?",
            "answer": 5,
            "user": 5,
            "correct": true
          },
          {
            "problem": "7 × 7 = ?",
            "answer": 49,
            "user": 49,
            "correct": true
          },
          {
            "problem": "1 × 8 = ?",
            "answer": 8,
            "user": 8,
            "correct": true
          },
          {
            "problem": "3 × 4 = ?",
            "answer": 12,
            "user": 12,
            "correct": true
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "division": {
      "best": {
        "score": 5,
        "total": 6,
        "timestamp": "2025-11-03T16:37:48.321355Z",
        "questions": [
          {
            "problem": "9 ÷ 9 = ?",
            "answer": 1,
            "user": 1,
            "correct": true
          },
          {
            "problem": "8 ÷ 4 = ?",
            "answer": 2,
            "user": 2,
            "correct": true
          },
          {
            "problem": "9 ÷ 1 = ?",
            "answer": 9,
            "user": 9,
            "correct": true
          },
          {
            "problem": "7 ÷ 7 = ?",
            "answer": 1,
            "user": 2,
            "correct": false
          },
          {
            "problem": "3 ÷ 1 = ?",
            "answer": 3,
            "user": 3,
            "correct": true
          },
          {
            "problem": "8 ÷ 4 = ?",
            "answer": 2,
            "user": 2,
            "correct": true
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "mix": {
      "best": {
        "score": 2,
        "total": 4,
        "timestamp": "2025-11-03T16:36:33.817060Z",
        "questions": [
          {
            "problem": "28 + 91 = ?",
            "answer": 119,
            "user": 121,
            "correct": false
          },
          {
            "problem": "88 - 62 = ?",
            "answer": 26,
            "user": 2342,
            "correct": false
          },
          {
            "problem": "3 ÷ 1 = ?",
            "answer": 3,
            "user": 3,
            "correct": true
          },
          {
            "problem": "16 + 15 = ?",
            "answer": 31,
            "user": 31,
            "correct": true
          }
        ]
      }
    }
  }
}